Hello!
If you are working in complex deals,
sales frameworks like Meddicc, Bant or
Spiced, can be invaluable tools to
qualify the deal, ask the right
questions, and progress the deal to
closure.
However, implementing these frameworks
in Zoho is often complex and
time-consuming.
With Meddicc Score, we’ve created the
simplest way to bring them to life —
using AI to automatically fill, score,
and coach your team with ease.
Let’s see it in action!
Imagine you are currently working on a
new deal that already has some records
such as notes, emails, calls or
meetings.
We can use this information to
automatically fill the framework form.
The Meddics Score card appears on your
list of items of your Deal record.
You can click on 'Refill' and the AI
will first use the existing information
to fill the selected framework form.
You can also add more information to
complete the questions.
Upon clicking on 'score' , the AI will
provide you with a score for the Deal,
individual feedback and recommend next
steps to progress to closure.
Meddicc score also provide a complete
report where you can see all the deals
where you need to focus on this
quarter.
What are their Scores, the amount or the
status.
So, ready to boost your sales?
Install Meddicc Score from the Zoho
marketplace and test it for free during
30 days!
Get started today!