Hello!.
Let’s explore the configuration and
settings available in Meddicc Score.
To access the settings, simply click at
the bottom of on any card.
.
If you’re an admin, you’ll have full
access to all configuration options.
There are four main sections in the
settings:
General, Company Profile, Frameworks,
and Users.
In the General section, you can manage
non-admin user access.
For example, if they can change the
framework or update the score manually.
You’ll also find automation options —
for example, when a new record is
added,if the deal is automatically
updated and score it.
Or score all the account at once, very
useful when you are starting with the
plug-in, to score all the hundreds of
deals you already have.
From here, you can also manage your
subscription, delete the Meddicc Score
account and all the data stored, and
handle billing directly through Stripe.
The scoring methodology can be
customized to score the form by section
or for the entire form althogheter
using AI.
And here’s something really powerful —
you can select your AI provider and
choose which LLM model you want to use
to power your insights.
In the Company Profile section, you can
add key information about your
organization — like your industry,
company name, value proposition, and
products or services.
This allows the AI to generate insights
that are fully tailored to your
business.
Next, the Frameworks section gives you
complete flexibility.
You can set a default framework for new
deals — for instance, Meddpic, spiced,
bant, or many others .
You can also edit the questions or
guidance, and even add or remove
questions to perfectly match your sales
process.
Finally, in the Users tab , you can view
all users in your account, check how
many licenses are available, and
upgrade, downgrade, or assign admin
rights in just a few clicks.
And that’s it!
With Meddicc Score, you have full
control and flexibility to tailor the
app to your sales methodology, your
team, and your business needs So, ready
to boost your sales?
Install Meddicc Score from the Hubspot
marketplace and test it for free during
30 days!
Get started today!