Hello!
If you are working in complex deals,
sales frameworks like Meddicc, Bant or
Spiced, can be invaluable tools to
qualify the deal, ask the right
questions, and progress the deal to
closure.
However, implementing these frameworks
in HubSpot is often complex and
time-consuming.
With Meddicc Score, we’ve created the
simplest way to bring them to life —
using AI to automatically fill, score,
and coach your team with ease.
Let’s see it in action!
Imagine you are currently working on a
new deal that already has some records
such as notes, emails, calls or
meetings.
We can use this information to
automatically fill the framework form.
The Meddics Score card appears on the
right side or in the middle of your
Deal record.
You can click on 'Update score' and the
AI will first use the existing
information to fill the selected
framework form.
You can also add more information to
complete the questions.
Upon clicking on 'score', the AI will
provide you with a score for the Deal,
individual feedback and recommend next
steps to progress to closure.
New record?
no worries, with automations whenever a
new record is logged, it will be
re-considered and the score will be
automatically updated.
Meddicc score can also be accessed from
the contact record.
There, you can view all the deals
associated with that contact, along
with a personalized action plan
featuring the recommended next steps
for them.
.
This includes potential talking points
and questions that you may ask the
contact to progress on the deal.
You even have an email already drafted,
tailored with the information from the
deal.
Similarly, in companies, you can find a
list of all the deals and contacts
related to that company with the key
information needed to progress on the
deal closure.
So, ready to boost your sales?
Install Meddicc Score from the Hubspot
marketplace and test it for free during
30 days!
Get started today!